Selected environment has value Y
Selected browser has value Y
Selected module has value Y
Record Activity testcases
Selected testcase has value Y
For demo we are just running 3 testcases
Jenkins home page
Click RecordActivityDriverTest to start the test run
Test run started
Displays Console Output Logs
Downloading and compiling required code files...
Selected testcases execution started...
IE Launched! You can see that in the taskbar
IE opens up
Login to OTP
Verifying Dashboard page
Verifying Admin page
Verifying Current Activities page
Record activity started..
Entering required details
Searches for imported SPV created by Selenium..
Imported SPV can also be seen in the logs
Selecting the desired SPV
On a new window Patient Page opens up to verify Imported Address
Verifying Address
Back to Record Activity Page
Verifying Activity Start, End Date and Duration
Verifying Finish Activity Page
Verifying required Text
Entering required inputs
Displays Current Activities Page
Entering filter criteria to search Finished Activities
Verifying output result
Logout from OTP and close the browser
Excel shows execution status separately